Guide to the Duke University Archives Photographic Negative Collection, 1855-1995
University Archives Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- Subject Negatives
  - Subject: Students - J
    - Students, Jefferson, A. W., 1975 December
    - Students, Jenkins, Kimberly
    - Students, Jenkins, M., 1980 January
    - Students, Jones, Ken, 1977 November
    - Students, Jones, Pam, 1977
  - Subject: Students - K
    - Students, Kars, Marjoleine, scholarship winner, 1978 September
    - Students, Kates, Mike, 1979 November
    - Students, Kathleen
    - Students, Kennedy, Joe, 1978 April
    - Students, Kiger, Glenn, 1980 October
    - Students, Kimbro, Steve, skiing on one leg, 1978
    - Students, King, L., 1976 December
    - Students, Kingsbury, 1978
    - Students, Kirchner, Gail
    - Students, Kish, Joy
    - Students, Kline, Larry, his daughter
    - Students, Knecht, Tim
    - Students, Knight, Catie
    - Students, Knight, Ravoy, 1981 March
    - Students, Krahn, Paula, 1979
    - Students, Kreines, Vivian
    - Students, Kreiter, Jo Ann, 1984 January
    - Students, Kress, Kenneth, 1978 September
    - Students, Kuntz, Don
  - Subject: Students - L
    - Students, Labelle, Ginger, 1979 January
    - Students, Lancaster, 1975 December
    - Students, Langford, Roberta, 1963
    - Students, Langston, Denzil
    - Students, Lapwing, 1975 March
    - Students, Lattimore, Caroline, 1977 January
    - Students, Laughlin, Brad, 1981 April
    - Students, Lazewski, Jennifer, 1986 February
    - Students, Leathers, Nancy, 1979 February
    - Students, Leininger, 1976 August
    - Students, Levin, Diane, 1980 October
    - Students, Lewis, passport
    - Students, Lewis, WR, 1963 May
    - Students, Lingler, Jim, 1982 August 5
    - Students, Llau?
    - Students, Lorber, Peter, 1982 November
    - Students, Low, Heather, 1965 February
    - Students, Lundberg, 1981 April
  - Subject: Students - Mc
    - Students, McBryde, A., Jr., 1962 May
    - Students, McConkey, David, 1980 April
    - Students, McDade, Lucinda, 1985 November
    - Students, McGill, Jim, 1982 November
    - Students, McDonald, Richard, 1981 March
  - Subject: Students - M
    - Students, Maffo, African graduate student
    - Students, Magot, Joan, 1976 March
    - Students, Maid of Cotton Candidate
    - Students, Maltese, John, 1978 November
    - Students, Maul, Elizabeth, August
    - Students, Meadows, Lin, 1977 August
    - Students, Mears, Julie, 1983 October
    - Students, Mia
    - Students, Miller, Curtis, 1975 November
    - Students, Miller, Mark R., Alcoa Scholarship, 1978 October
    - Students, Minah Twins, 1961
    - Students, Moore, Shelley
    - Students, Mori, Yukio, 1977 May
    - Students, Morgan, Barbara, NC Dairy Princess, 1962 April
    - Students, Mumford, Rich, 1980 April
    - Students, Munfort, Richard, 1978 November
    - Students, Munger or Munyer, Walter
    - Students, Murrah, Bobby, 1983 February
  - Subject: Students - N
    - Students, Nance, RL, 1961 September
    - Students, Nelson, Carol, scholarship winner, 1981 October
    - Students, Nigerian girl in native clothes, 1969 February
    - Students, North, Terri, P.E. award, 1979 April
  - Subject: Students - P
    - Students, Pardo, Steve
    - Students, Parkey, John Edward, 1981 March
    - Students, Peckham, Debbie, 1981 March
    - Students, Peroutka, Bob, 1977 April
    - Students, Peterson, Laura, 1976
    - Students, Potter, Jeff, 1977 September
    - Students, Potter, Jerry
    - Students, Powell, Alton, 1977 September
  - Subject: Students - R
    - Students, Rainer, Randell, ASDU president, 1985 November
    - Students, Rainey, Waverly, 1979
    - Students, Reinecke, Peter, 1982 October
    - Students, Reynolds, Dave, 1982 August
    - Students, Rho, Tae, 1979 August
    - Students, Richey, 1961 November
    - Students, Rives, M.
    - Students, Robin, engineering
    - Students, Roessler, Ralph, 1984 September
    - Students, Ropp, Elizabeth, 1976 May
    - Students, Rosshirt, David, 1981 April
    - Students, Rome
  - Subject: Students - S
    - Students, Salinger, Jill, 1963 February
    - Students, Saltzman, David, 1980 October
    - Students, Sander, Stephen, 1984 January
    - Students, Schaffer, Jim
    - Students, Schaeffer, Nikki, 1983 November
    - Students, Schneider, Mary, 1980 October
    - Students, Schnake, Carol, 1977 July
    - Students, Schultz, Chris, 1986 January
    - Students, Scott, Debbie, 1983 May
    - Students, Scruggs, Karen, 1979 March
    - Students, Shapiro, 1980 April
    - Students, Shapperd, Gretchen
    - Students, Shaw, Charles, 1975 April
    - Students, Shield, John
    - Students, Simon, S., 1962 March
    - Students, Smith, Amy, 1983 April
    - Students, Smith, Culver H.
    - Students, Smith, Cynthia, 1978 March
    - Students, Smith, 1984 July
    - Students, Smith, Katherine, 1978 October
    - Students, Smith, Linwood, 1977 March
    - Students, Smith, Linwood, 1977 September
    - Students, Smith, Lynn, 1958 May
    - Students, Snowhite, Jennifer
    - Students, Snowhite, Jennifer, 1981 April
    - Students, Soddrell, D., 1982 May
    - Students, Sparkman, Jody, 1975 November
    - Students, Sparkman, Jody
    - Students, Specht, Tom, 1984 October
    - Students, Spudis, Barbara, 1977 November
    - Students, Sronce, ? John
    - Students, Stephens, girl, 1963 December
    - Students, Stevens, Phyllis, 1958 April
    - Students, Still, Chris, 1986 January
    - Students, Strickland, Adrian
    - Students, Strickland, Adrianne, 1979 April
    - Students, Sugg, Nancy, 1977 March
    - Students, Sugg, Nancy, 1977 September
  - Subject: Students - T
    - Students, Tanner, Joe, 1957 June
    - Students, Taylor, George, 1976 May
    - Students, Tesluk, Greg, 1976 October
    - Students, Thomas, Mark, soccer
    - Students, Tiryakian, Edwyn, 1982 February
    - Students, Tifft, 1973 July
    - Students, Travis, Joe, 1976
    - Students, Trawick, Janice, 1975 January
    - Students, Tucker, Nina, 1981 January
    - Students, Turton, Debbie, 1975
    - Students, twins, 1957 October
  - Subject: Students - V
    - Students, Vanderwist, Lynn, 1975 April
    - Students, Versfelt, Joseph, 1984 December
    - Students, Vollinger, Bob, 1984 January
  - Subject: Students - W
    - Students, Walker, Barbara
    - Students, Ware, Russell
    - Students, Warren, Henry, 1975 April
    - Students, Washburn, Ron, 1979 May
    - Students, Wharton, Emily, 1985 October
    - Students, White
    - Students, Wiedman, Mary Ann, 1984 February
    - Students, Wiley, Sally, 1979 April
    - Students, Wiley
    - Students, Williams, 1978 July
    - Students, Wilson
    - Students, Wilson, K.
    - Students, Windsor, scholarship winner, development, 1978 January
    - Students, Wol, Larry, 1975 March
    - Students, Wood, Jay, 1962 May
    - Students, Wright, John D.
  - Subject: Students - Y
    - Students, Youngkin, and wife, 1961
  - Subject: Students - Z
    - Students, Zappa, Gina, P.E. award, 1979 April
  - Subject: Trustees - A
    - Trustees, Alderman, Sidney S., 1958 February
    - Trustees, Aldridge, TA, 1959 June
    - Trustees, Allen, George, 1961 November
    - Trustees, Allen, George, 1965 September
    - Trustees, Alspaugh, Col. J.W., 1968 September
  - Subject: Trustees - B
    - Trustees, Bowles, Charles Phillips, 1954 June 20
    - Trustees, Bradshaw, 1959 February
    - Trustees, Bradshaw, RW, 1959 February
    - Trustees, Brian, Mrs. Earl, 1967
    - Trustees, Brim, Kenneth, 1953 April 30
    - Trustees, Brown, Joseph Gill, 1967 August
    - Trustees, Brown, Werner, 1971 March
    - Trustees, Bruton, John F., 1967 August
    - Trustees, Burkhead, Rev. LS, 1968 August
  - Subject: Trustees - C
    - Trustees, Cannon, CA, 1963 December
    - Trustees, Cannon, Biship WR, 1970 June
    - Trustees, Chandler, John Wesley, 1987 October
    - Trustees, Clegg, Charles, 1954 June
    - Trustees, Clegg, William L., 1961
    - Trustees, Cocke, Norman, 1958 November
    - Trustees, Cook, Samuel DuBois, 1987 October
    - Trustees, Cranford, Chairman of the Board
    - Trustees, Craven, Braxton, Jr., 1971 March
    - Trustees, Cunningham, 1963 June
  - Subject: Trustees - D
    - Trustees, Donnell, Edward S., 1987 October
  - Subject: Trustees - E
    - Trustees, Endowment Committee, 1961 December
  - Subject: Trustees - F
    - Trustees, Few, Ben F., 1967
    - Trustees, Finch, Thomas A., 1963 November
    - Trustees, Fuqua, JB, 1980 October
  - Subject: Trustees - G
    - Trustees, Garrett, Nathan T., 1987 October
  - Subject: Trustees - H
    - Trustees, Hanes, P. Huber, Jr., 1954 June 20
    - Trustees, Hanks, Nancy, Wright Tisdale, Douglas Knight, 1966 November
    - Trustees, Hanks, Nancy, 1966 July
    - Trustees, Hardin, Paul, 1971 August
    - Trustees, Harris, 1954 November
    - Trustees, Hart, Milledge A., III, 1987 October
    - Trustees, Herbert, George Richard, 1987 October
    - Trustees, Hoadley, Walter E., 1967
    - Trustees, Houck, CB, 1967 December
    - Trustees, Hunt with Mr. Tisdale and Dr. Knight, 1967 March
    - Trustees, Hunt, Alfred M., 1967 February
  - Subject: Trustees - I
    - Trustees, Ivey, George M., 1950 December
    - Trustees, Ivey, George M., Sr., 1964
  - Subject: Trustees - J
    - Trustees, Johnson, Jeff, 1951 March
    - Trustees, Jones, Edwin, 1956 October
    - Trustees, Jones, Edwin, Jr., 1952 December
    - Trustees, Jones, Edwin Lee, 1967
    - Trustees, Jones, Edwin L., Jr.
    - Trustees, Jones, JA, 1980 March
    - Trustees, Jordan, BE, 1952 May 7
  - Subject: Trustees - K
    - Trustees, Kearns, Amos, 1968 October
    - Trustees, Kempner Foundation, 1950 October 16
    - Trustees, Kurswell, Jeff, 1975
  - Subject: Trustees - Mc
    - Trustees, McMahon, Alex, 1981 January
  - Subject: Trustees - N
    - Trustees, Nasher, Raymond, 1973
  - Subject: Trustees - P
    - Trustees, Perkins, 1961
    - Trustees, Perry, Clifford W., 1971 March
    - Trustees, Pickens, Marshall, 1969 October
    - Trustees, Pierce, F. Grainger, 1954 March 16
    - Trustees, Pinnix, RH, 1959 June
    - Trustees, Pinnix, RH, 1961
    - Trustees, Pinnix, RH, 1961 September
    - Trustees, Pitts, Dr. William R., 1967
  - Subject: Trustees - R
    - Trustees, Rauch, Henry E., 1964 June
    - Trustees, Rhyne, Charles, 1973
    - Trustees, Robertson, Rubin B., 1957 March
  - Subject: Trustees - S (Box 23)
    - Trustees, Sherrill, Frank
    - Trustees, Smith, JR, 1967 December
    - Trustees, Smith, Willis
    - Trustees, Southgate, TF, Jr., 1959 February
    - Trustees, Southgate, James, 1968 October
    - Trustees, Spears, Mrs. Marshall, 1967 December
  - Subject: Trustees - T
    - Trustees, Temple, Arthur, 1983 October
    - Trustees, Thigpen, 1959 September
    - Trustees, Tinsdale and Wright, 1964 May
    - Trustees, Towe, Kenneth C., 1954 June 20
    - Trustees, Troika, 1969 June
    - Trustees, 1941 May 31
    - Trustees, Board of, 1947 November 26
    - Trustees, group, 1954
    - Trustees, with Edens and portrait of Allen, 1955 September
    - Trustees, group, 1958 November
    - Trustees, Executive Committee, 1960
    - Trustees, meeting, M. Semans first meeting, 1962 March
    - Trustees, Executive Committee, 1962 November
    - Trustees, oldest two, Womble, Mayer, newest, McGee, 1963 March
    - Trustees, 1963 March
    - Trustees, new, Rauch, Upchurch, Wade, Ivey, Tinsdale, 1964 December
    - Trustees, Allen, Tinsdale, Knight, 1965 March
    - Trustees, 1968 February
    - Trustees, group in board room, 1977 March 1
    - Trustees, Hill, Warren, Rice, Andek, 1987 August
  - Subject: Trustees - U
    - Trustees, Upchurch, Walter
  - Subject: Trustees - V
    - Trustees, Von Canon, JR, 1959 June
    - Trustees, Von Canon, 1984 February
  - Subject: Trustees - W
    - Trustees, Wade, Charles B., Jr., 1964 June
    - Trustees, Wade, Jones, Perry
    - Trustees, Wallace, George R., 1954 March 16
    - Trustees, Watson, Brantley, 1967
    - Trustees, Weldon, Rev. Wilson O., 1967
    - Trustees, Werber, WM
    - Trustees, Werber, Bill, 1951 June
    - Trustees, Westmoreland, 1977 June
    - Trustees, William, Neil, 1983 September
    - Trustees, Wilson, Henry H., 1971 March
    - Trustees, Wilson, Nathan Hunt Daniel, 1968 November
    - Trustees, Womble and map, 1963
    - Trustees, Womble, 1963 March
    - Trustees, Womble and Rounds, 1963 June
    - Trustees, Womble, 1961
  - Subject: Trustees - Y
    - Trustees, Younger, Kenneth Glen, Jr., 1987 October
  - Subject: Gardens
    - Gardens, visitors, 1936
    - Gardens, construction of, 1934-1935
    - Gardens, formal construction, 1937 November 9
    - Gardens, formal construction, 1938
    - Gardens, Jonquils, 1938
    - Gardens, flowers at Dr. Flowers' residence, 1938 March 19
    - Gardens, flower gardens, Woman's College, 1938 June
    - Gardens, 1939 April
    - Gardens, pool, circa late 1930s-early 1940s
    - Gardens, pool
    - Gardens, rock garden, 1939-1940
    - Gardens, aerial views, 1940 Summer
    - Gardens, in snow, 1940
    - Gardens, statues and ornaments, 1940
    - Gardens, people
    - Gardens, 1940
    - Gardens, gate and bridge, 1940-1944
    - Gardens, dogwood near biology, 1940 April 16
    - Gardens, hyacinths, 1940 April 16
    - Gardens, pansy bed, 1940 April 16
    - Gardens, 1940 April 28
    - Gardens, iris, 1940 May
    - Gardens, tulips, 1940 May
    - Gardens, 1940 May
    - Gardens, hollyhocks, 1940 May 19
    - Gardens, lotus, 1940 July 19
    - Gardens, walkways, 1940-1941
    - Gardens, views, 1941 April 13
    - Gardens, 1946-1947
    - Gardens, 1948
    - Gardens, spring, 1948
    - Gardens, crowds, 1950 April
    - Gardens, 1952 March
    - Gardens, foreman, 1954 September
    - Gardens, 1954
    - Gardens, 1955
    - Gardens, snow, 1956
    - Gardens, 1955
    - Gardens, views, 1955 October
    - Gardens, student in, 1956 March
    - Gardens, 1956 April
    - Gardens, 1957 March
    - Gardens, kid, 1958 April
    - Gardens, people, 1958 April
    - Gardens, water lilies, 1959 July
    - Gardens, new plants, 1959 September
    - Gardens, girls, 1960 March
    - Gardens, surveyors, 1960 April
    - Gardens, 1960 May
    - Gardens, gate designer, 1961 December
    - Gardens, gates, 1962 February
    - Gardens, wide angle, 1962 March
    - Gardens, renovation, 1962 December
    - Gardens, renovations, 1963 January
    - Gardens, 1963 June
    - Gardens, drawing, 1963 December
    - Gardens, aerial, 1964 May
    - Gardens, girl in, 1965 April
    - Gardens, Japanese family, 1965 May
    - Gardens, gates, main entrance, 1968 August
    - Gardens, flowering tree, 1976
    - Gardens, 1979 October
    - Gardens
    - Gardens, Mary Jo Strowd and Madge Slaughter
    - Gardens, lily pads
    - Gardens, ice on tree in garden, burst water line in winter
    - Gardens, map, proposed garden increase, 1960 February
    - Gardens, Duke
    - Gardens, color slides
    - Gardens, pond, 1940 March 20
  - Subject: Aerial Views
    - Aerial Views, campus from top of Allen building, 1963
    - Aerial Views, of Durham
    - Aerial Views, golf course
    - Aerial Views, drawings, East and West Campus, 1956 September
    - Aerial Views, drawings, East and West Campus, 1962 March
    - Aerial Views, West Campus, 1958
    - Aerial Views, East Campus
    - Aerial Views, East Campus and surrounding areas, 1940 July 18
    - Aerial Views, East Campus, 1958 May
    - Aerial Views, East Campus, 1940 July 20
    - Aerial Views, East Campus
    - Aerial Views, East Campus, 1967
    - Aerial Views, East Campus, low, looking north, 1963 October
    - Aerial Views, East Campus, 1951
    - Aerial Views, East Campus, Gilbert-Addoms, 1959
    - Aerial Views, East Campus, Gilbert-Addoms, looking north, 1963 October
    - Aerial Views, East Campus, Pegram, Bassett, Baldwin, looking north, 1963 October
    - Aerial Views, West Campus and Medical Center, 1970
    - Aerial Views, West Campus, looking west, 1970
    - Aerial Views, West Campus, looking northwest, 1970
    - Aerial Views, West Campus, looking northwest
    - Aerial Views, West Campus and Medical Center
    - Aerial Views, gardens, looking northeast, 1963 October
    - Aerial Views, gardens, looking south, 1963 October
    - Aerial Views, West Campus, Wallace Wade Stadium, looking south to north, 1942
    - Aerial Views, West Campus, new dorms, 1966 December
    - Aerial Views, Chapel, 1940s
    - Aerial Views, from top of Chapel, winter light, 1960 March
    - Aerial Views, clubhouse at Duke course, 1963 October
    - Aerial Views, quad, Chapel, 1955
    - Aerial Views, back of Chapel, 1957 September
    - Aerial Views, West Campus, 1956
    - Aerial Views, Bell Building
    - Aerial Views, 10,000 feet, 1957 November
    - Aerial Views, West Campus, center of campus and drive from circle, 1963 October
    - Aerial Views, AROD, North building, 1963 October
    - Aerial Views, Chapel area, 1959
    - Aerial Views, West Campus, 1940
    - Aerial Views, West Campus, quad, 1963 October
    - Aerial Views, West Campus, before Allen Building, 1953
    - Aerial Views, West Campus
    - Aerial Views, West Campus, 1967 December
    - Aerial Views, golf course, 9th green and clubhouse, 1960 January
    - Aerial Views, golf course, 1963 October
    - Aerial Views, graduate student apartments, 1963 October
    - Aerial Views, hospital, 1956 April
    - Aerial Views, new hospital wing, 1957 November
    - Aerial Views, hospital, 1957 October
    - Aerial Views, hospital, 1963 March
    - Aerial Views, hospital
    - Aerial Views, hospital front looking southeast, 1963 October
    - Aerial Views, law school, 1963 October
    - Aerial Views, marine lab, 1966 June
    - Aerial Views, marine lab, 1982
    - Aerial Views, medical center, 1967
    - Aerial Views, medical center, 1985 May
    - Aerial Views, medical research park behind AROD, 1970
    - Aerial Views, medical center front and part of campus looking south, 1963 October
    - Aerial Views, physics building, construction, 1963 October
    - Aerial Views, West Campus, quad, showing relation to Duke Gardens, 1963 October
    - Aerial Views, West Campus, Union, Chapel, Flowers, Gray, Divinity, looking northwest, 1963 October
    - Aerial Views, Science Drive
    - Aerial Views, East Campus, Southgate, 1963 October
    - Aerial Views, West Campus, stadium, athletic area, looking northwest, 1963 October
    - Aerial Views, West Campus, stadium, 1964 November
    - Aerial Views, stadium area, 1940
    - Aerial Views, vet med compound, 1970 September
    - Aerial Views, West Campus looking north, 1963 October
    - Aerial Views, West Campus looking south, 1963 October
    - Aerial Views, West Campus, 1962 March
    - Aerial Views, West Campus, 1941
    - Aerial Views, West Campus
    - Aerial Views, West Campus, 1940
    - Aerial Views, West Campus, 1986 March
    - Aerial Views, East Campus
    - Aerial Views, West Campus with golf course
    - Aerial Views, Chapel and Quad, 1940 April 15
    - Aerial Views, center Quad
  - Subject: Development
    - Development, Dr. Edens receiving check, 1956 December
    - Development, Dr. Parker and check, 1971
    - Development, Dr. Anlyan and Wilbanks, check presentation, 1965 November
    - Development, award to man from Montgomery Ward, 1984
    - Development, check from local bank, 1980 January
    - Development, Dr. Bassett and CW Whitefield, check presentation, 1965 July
    - Development, unidentified man, copy for Brenda Hayes, 1985 August
    - Development, Mr. and Mrs. Chadwick, 1979 February
    - Development, check, Honeywell with Terry Sanford, 1980 March
    - Development, check, 1983 March
    - Development, cancer check, 1982 January
    - Development, Pye receiving check, 1981 October
    - Development, gift check to Provost, 1981 April
    - Development, Terry Sanford and McMahon with "dummy" check, 1980
    - Development, check presentation, 1981 February
    - Development, campaign kick-off, press, TV, 1966 Summer
    - Development, copy of chart, 1974 July
    - Development, charts, future planning, 1965 September
    - Development, master chart, future development, 1965 September
    - Development, check to Kenneth Pye, 1977
    - Development, check to Kenneth Pye, 1977 September 8
    - Development, check from Alcoa, 1977 May
    - Development, Alcoa check presentation, 1965 May
    - Development, oil check to Terry Sanford, 1975
    - Development, American Oil check presentation, 1965 November
    - Development, American Oil check, 1973
    - Development, check from Amoco, 1970
    - Development, check from American Oil Co., 1967 November
    - Development, American Oil check presentation to Mr. Huestis, 1966 November
    - Development, check from Bache, 1973 October
    - Development, Blackburn check presentation, 1975 August
    - Development, check from Bell Systems, 1968 December
    - Development, Chemstrand gift, 1964 July
    - Development, check from Citgo oil, Huestis, 1976 February
    - Development, Ken Pye and check from Dupont, 1977 February
    - Development, check to civil engineer, 1975 January
    - Development, Eastman check, 1972 November
    - Development, Erwin Oil check presentation, 1964 December
    - Development, check from Esso, 1965 December
    - Development, check, General Electric, 1972
    - Development, check from Gulf, 1977 March 1
    - Development, check from Gulf, 1975
    - Development, gift from Gulf corporation, 1965 June
    - Development, check from Humble Oil, 1969
    - Development, check for mental research center, 1966 January
    - Development, NCNB check presentation, 1969 July
    - Development, check presentation to President Sanford, 1971 October
    - Development, foundation check to student union, 1965 September
    - Development, check from Sears and Co., 1977 February
    - Development, Sears check, 1975 January
    - Development, Sears check presentation to library, 1973 November
    - Development, Sears check presentation, 1966 December
    - Development, Dr. Knight receiving Sears check, 1964 November
    - Development, check from Traveler's Insurance, 1970
    - Development, Upjohn check presentation, 1968 October
    - Development, US Steel check presentation, 1970
    - Development, US Steel check presentation, 1968 May
    - Development, Huestis and T. Cole receiving check from US Steel, 1967 June
    - Development, US Steel check presentation, 1966 September
    - Development, US Steel grant, 1965 June
    - Development, check from US Steel, 1964 June
    - Development, Pye, Western Electric check, 1977 March
    - Development, Westinghouse gift, 1969 September
    - Development, Mrs. Paul Clyde
    - Development, Duke-Durham Fund, Sanford and Chairman, 1978 January
    - Development, Denise, 1982 April
    - Development, staff, 1982 March
    - Development, check from Dupont, 1979 March
    - Development, driver training center at RTP, 1972
    - Development, floor plan, driver training center at RTP, 1972
    - Development, check to engineer, Huestis, 1979 August 20
    - Development, Eastman chem. school, 1972 April
    - Development, epoch campaign, 1973 December
    - Development, WC Brown, fifth decade campaign leader, 1967 November
    - Development, 187 million fund drive kickoff, 1965 June
    - Development, dollar bill, 1970 May
    - Development, silver dollar, 1980 May
    - Development, Duke-Durham Fund, Chairman Alexander and Terry Sanford, 1979 January 8
    - Development, President Sanford, fundraising breakfast, Duke-Liggett Myers, 1975 April
    - Development, copies from archives, 1981 January
    - Development, copies for publication, 1977 September
    - Development, check from Westinghouse, 1980 February
    - Development, 1978 September
    - Development, Alzheimer's Disease sign, 1983 August
- General Negatives
  - General - A (Box 24)
    - Adams Family, feature, 1954 November
    - Admissions, student application, 1968 January